http://www.skydive.ie/cookie-policy

Skip to contentFacebook page opens in new windowinfo@skydive.ieClonbullogue Airfield, Edenderry, Co. Offaly046 973 0103HomeBook your SkydiveTandem Christmas SpecialCouples Xmas Tandem SkydiveEasy Pay Christmas SpecialVoucher €100.00Voucher €50.00Solo JumpAssisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 1Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 1-7Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 2-3Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 4-7Charity Parachute JumpsPro SkydiverSocial WallPhotosVideosTestimonialsNewsAbout UsFAQOur HistoryFacilitiesMeet the TeamCharity Skydive RequirementsContact UsCookie PolicyYou are here:HomeCookie PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://skydive.ie.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsOur contact form collects your name, phone number, and email so you can be contacted. This information will only be used to reply to your inquiry.CookiesCookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that the website can “remember” you on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the website.If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Irish Parachute Club uses cookies to collect information about visitors’ use of the website, including things like connection speed, operating system details, the time and duration visits and IP addresses. The information collected by cookies enables Irish Parachute Club to understand the use of its site, including the number of visitors it has, the pages viewed per session, time exposed to particular pages etc. This in turn helps to provide visitors with a better experience. Irish Parachute Club will not attempt to personally identify visitors from their IP addresses, which are anonymized.Cookies do not in any way compromise the security of your computer. Visitors can use most of Irish Parachute Club’s website with no loss of functionality if cookies are disabled from the web browser.Irish Parachute Club uses the following cookie types:FunctionalityThese cookies allow Irish Parachute Club’s website to remember choices you make (such as your preferred language) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. Other examples include cookies that keep track of your progress when filling online application forms.PerformanceThese cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. Irish Parachute Club uses first-party analytics cookies for this purpose.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.For more information about how to manage cookies, including opting-out of different types of cookies please visit: www.aboutcookies.orgYou can also find more information about how to opt-out of targeting cookies by visiting: www.youronlinechoices.comPlease take note of the following information with regard to the third party cookies used on our website:Google Universal AnalyticsWhat is Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies in order to evaluate your use of Irish Parachute Club’s website. Browsers do not share cookies across domains.How Google Analytics WorksGoogle do not collect or store personal information. Google Analytics prohibits the tracking or collection of personal information or association of personal information with web analytics information. Google Analytics does not report the actual IP address information to Google Analytics customers.What Google Analytic Features are enabled by Irish Parachute Club:The following Google Analytics features are enabled in respect of Irish Parachute Club’s use of Google Analytics:User ID -This allows Irish Parachute Club to associate multiple sessions (and any activity within those sessions) with a unique ID, in this case an ID derived from online interactions with Irish Parachute Club. When the unique ID and any related engagement data is sent to Google Analytics, all activity is attributed to one anonymous user who is not personally identifiable in the reports.With the unique ID, Irish Parachute Club can get a more accurate user count, analyse the signed-in user experience, and get access to the new cross device reports.While Google Analytic cookies are targeting cookies which use a unique ID and can track your visits around different websites, the information collected is anonymous and you will not be personally identifiable to either Google or Irish Parachute Club.Demographics and interests reporting – Understand how Irish Parachute Club’s site audience breaks down by age, gender, and interests.Google analytics data sharing settings enabled: Google products & services – Irish Parachute Club shares Google Analytics data with Google to help improve Google’s products and servicesBenchmarking – Irish Parachute Club contributes anonymous data to an aggregate data set to enable features like benchmarking and publications that can help Irish Parachute Club understand data trends. All identifiable information about Irish Parachute Club’s website is removed and combined with other anonymous data before it is shared with others.Technical support – Google technical support representatives have access to Irish Parachute Club’s Google Analytics data and account when necessary to provide service and find solutions to technical issues.Opt-out: Users may opt-out of Google Universal Analytics use of cookies by visiting the Google Universal Analytics opt-out page.Storage Location: Google stores the information collected by the cookie on secure Google servers.FacebookFacebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanationHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Recent ArticlesGuidelines For The Return to Normal Operations17th June 2020XMAS SPECIAL OFFERS23rd November 2018CLOSED 10TH & 11TH OF NOVEMBER9th November 2018Making History7th November 2018Our New Baby!!!1st November 2018WEEKEND OPENING TIMES19th October 2018Weather Forecast
The location could not be found.Recent CommentsSolo JumpTandem SkydiveAssisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 1Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 1-7Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 2-3Assisted Free Fall ‘AFF’ Level 4-7Voucher €50.00Voucher €100.00Charity Parachute Jumps Go to Top
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.AcceptCookie Policy
